{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742640665","data":{"timestamp":" 947742640665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742643866","data":{"timestamp":" 947742643864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742646279","data":{"timestamp":" 947742646278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742648970","data":{"timestamp":" 947742648969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742652142","data":{"timestamp":" 947742652142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742654672","data":{"timestamp":" 947742654670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742665486","data":{"timestamp":" 947742665486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742670002","data":{"timestamp":" 947742670002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742671654","data":{"timestamp":" 947742671653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742673482","data":{"timestamp":" 947742673482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742676406","data":{"timestamp":" 947742676405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742680342","data":{"timestamp":" 947742680341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742684875","data":{"timestamp":" 947742684875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742687499","data":{"timestamp":" 947742687499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEKUFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742690880","data":{"timestamp":" 947742690879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742694634","data":{"timestamp":" 947742694634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742697886","data":{"timestamp":" 947742697885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742703076","data":{"timestamp":" 947742703075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742706913","data":{"timestamp":" 947742706913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742710825","data":{"timestamp":" 947742710825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742721444","data":{"timestamp":" 947742721444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742724222","data":{"timestamp":" 947742724221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742727086","data":{"timestamp":" 947742727086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742730708","data":{"timestamp":" 947742730708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742737104","data":{"timestamp":" 947742737103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742742916","data":{"timestamp":" 947742742916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYETAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742748628","data":{"timestamp":" 947742748628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742754186","data":{"timestamp":" 947742754186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742756851","data":{"timestamp":" 947742756850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742762354","data":{"timestamp":" 947742762354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742768425","data":{"timestamp":" 947742768425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742771251","data":{"timestamp":" 947742771251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742781421","data":{"timestamp":" 947742781420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742783735","data":{"timestamp":" 947742783735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYENYEKEVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742786624","data":{"timestamp":" 947742786624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYAMAVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742790317","data":{"timestamp":" 947742790317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742792993","data":{"timestamp":" 947742792992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742795538","data":{"timestamp":" 947742795538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742797694","data":{"timestamp":" 947742797693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742804285","data":{"timestamp":" 947742804285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742807156","data":{"timestamp":" 947742807156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742809136","data":{"timestamp":" 947742809135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742812808","data":{"timestamp":" 947742812808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742815907","data":{"timestamp":" 947742815907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUMSIKIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742818019","data":{"timestamp":" 947742818019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742821614","data":{"timestamp":" 947742821614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAJALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742827252","data":{"timestamp":" 947742827251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742830602","data":{"timestamp":" 947742830602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742835798","data":{"timestamp":" 947742835798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742842101","data":{"timestamp":" 947742842101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742846045","data":{"timestamp":" 947742846044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742849022","data":{"timestamp":" 947742849021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742853532","data":{"timestamp":" 947742853531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742862910","data":{"timestamp":" 947742862909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742868038","data":{"timestamp":" 947742868038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742872173","data":{"timestamp":" 947742872173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742877342","data":{"timestamp":" 947742877342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742879810","data":{"timestamp":" 947742879809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742884889","data":{"timestamp":" 947742884889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742888593","data":{"timestamp":" 947742888592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742891560","data":{"timestamp":" 947742891560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742897937","data":{"timestamp":" 947742897937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742901335","data":{"timestamp":" 947742901335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742904765","data":{"timestamp":" 947742904765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742910534","data":{"timestamp":" 947742910534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742913775","data":{"timestamp":" 947742913775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742916962","data":{"timestamp":" 947742916962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742918767","data":{"timestamp":" 947742918767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742922013","data":{"timestamp":" 947742922013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742924611","data":{"timestamp":" 947742924611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742928019","data":{"timestamp":" 947742928018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742932080","data":{"timestamp":" 947742932080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742935968","data":{"timestamp":" 947742935968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742942347","data":{"timestamp":" 947742942346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742951780","data":{"timestamp":" 947742951780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742956534","data":{"timestamp":" 947742956534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742958579","data":{"timestamp":" 947742958579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742964987","data":{"timestamp":" 947742964987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742968314","data":{"timestamp":" 947742968314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742976198","data":{"timestamp":" 947742976198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742980175","data":{"timestamp":" 947742980175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742982160","data":{"timestamp":" 947742982160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742991879","data":{"timestamp":" 947742991879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NETASILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742995844","data":{"timestamp":" 947742995844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMINIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742998769","data":{"timestamp":" 947742998769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPEANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743002086","data":{"timestamp":" 947743002086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAJIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743011835","data":{"timestamp":" 947743011834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NETASILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743015463","data":{"timestamp":" 947743015463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743017273","data":{"timestamp":" 947743017273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743020370","data":{"timestamp":" 947743020370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGONJWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743022519","data":{"timestamp":" 947743022519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743024781","data":{"timestamp":" 947743024780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743027599","data":{"timestamp":" 947743027599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743029292","data":{"timestamp":" 947743029292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743033137","data":{"timestamp":" 947743033137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743037058","data":{"timestamp":" 947743037058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743043755","data":{"timestamp":" 947743043754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDONDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743047344","data":{"timestamp":" 947743047343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743049991","data":{"timestamp":" 947743049991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743052818","data":{"timestamp":" 947743052818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743054658","data":{"timestamp":" 947743054657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743057726","data":{"timestamp":" 947743057725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743060182","data":{"timestamp":" 947743060182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMWITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743063681","data":{"timestamp":" 947743063681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743066581","data":{"timestamp":" 947743066581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743068614","data":{"timestamp":" 947743068614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743070568","data":{"timestamp":" 947743070568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743072904","data":{"timestamp":" 947743072903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unatoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNATOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743075120","data":{"timestamp":" 947743075120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unatoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743077377","data":{"timestamp":" 947743077377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakwenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743079623","data":{"timestamp":" 947743079623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakwenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743082592","data":{"timestamp":" 947743082592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743084669","data":{"timestamp":" 947743084669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743088149","data":{"timestamp":" 947743088149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743090370","data":{"timestamp":" 947743090370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743092590","data":{"timestamp":" 947743092590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743096767","data":{"timestamp":" 947743096767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743099744","data":{"timestamp":" 947743099744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743101585","data":{"timestamp":" 947743101584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743104963","data":{"timestamp":" 947743104963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNIBEBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743109725","data":{"timestamp":" 947743109725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNIPELEKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743112718","data":{"timestamp":" 947743112718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743115665","data":{"timestamp":" 947743115665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743125298","data":{"timestamp":" 947743125297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743129955","data":{"timestamp":" 947743129955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKWAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743131531","data":{"timestamp":" 947743131531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743133997","data":{"timestamp":" 947743133997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743139699","data":{"timestamp":" 947743139699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743141957","data":{"timestamp":" 947743141956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONYESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743143716","data":{"timestamp":" 947743143716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743147174","data":{"timestamp":" 947743147174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743149049","data":{"timestamp":" 947743149049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743150618","data":{"timestamp":" 947743150618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743152341","data":{"timestamp":" 947743152341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743155406","data":{"timestamp":" 947743155406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIGUSE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743158299","data":{"timestamp":" 947743158299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743160321","data":{"timestamp":" 947743160321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDONDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743162082","data":{"timestamp":" 947743162082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743164132","data":{"timestamp":" 947743164132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743166571","data":{"timestamp":" 947743166571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743168621","data":{"timestamp":" 947743168621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743177807","data":{"timestamp":" 947743177807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743180315","data":{"timestamp":" 947743180315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743182846","data":{"timestamp":" 947743182846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743184677","data":{"timestamp":" 947743184677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743186230","data":{"timestamp":" 947743186230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743186425","data":{"timestamp":" 947743186425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743188636","data":{"timestamp":" 947743188636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743190723","data":{"timestamp":" 947743190723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743192700","data":{"timestamp":" 947743192700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743195242","data":{"timestamp":" 947743195242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743197432","data":{"timestamp":" 947743197432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743199679","data":{"timestamp":" 947743199679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JONGOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743201367","data":{"timestamp":" 947743201367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743203195","data":{"timestamp":" 947743203195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743205117","data":{"timestamp":" 947743205117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743208623","data":{"timestamp":" 947743208623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743211930","data":{"timestamp":" 947743211930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743214116","data":{"timestamp":" 947743214116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743216324","data":{"timestamp":" 947743216324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMECHOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743218042","data":{"timestamp":" 947743218042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743220907","data":{"timestamp":" 947743220907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUDHOOFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743227280","data":{"timestamp":" 947743227280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743235423","data":{"timestamp":" 947743235422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743238106","data":{"timestamp":" 947743238105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743240503","data":{"timestamp":" 947743240503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKETI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743250978","data":{"timestamp":" 947743250978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743930716","data":{"timestamp":" 947743930716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743930824","data":{"timestamp":" 947743930824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743930990","data":{"timestamp":" 947743930990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743939346","data":{"timestamp":" 947743939346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 9dc7096e-0522-4ced-8678-4981c3b6c939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743952464","data":{"timestamp":" 947743952464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHAYANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743954785","data":{"timestamp":" 947743954785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743956394","data":{"timestamp":" 947743956393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743959243","data":{"timestamp":" 947743959242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743970096","data":{"timestamp":" 947743970095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743975586","data":{"timestamp":" 947743975586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947743977550","data":{"timestamp":" 947743977550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769518716","data":{"timestamp":" 947769518715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769524103","data":{"timestamp":" 947769524103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769533897","data":{"timestamp":" 947769533896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769540449","data":{"timestamp":" 947769540449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_75","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769551028","data":{"timestamp":" 947769551028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 4d43e652-ad9b-4e84-8b63-7f89e69d95d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769560095","data":{"timestamp":" 947769560094"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769560329","data":{"timestamp":" 947769560329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769561303","data":{"timestamp":" 947769561302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769562589","data":{"timestamp":" 947769562588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769565558","data":{"timestamp":" 947769565557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769566413","data":{"timestamp":" 947769566412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769566736","data":{"timestamp":" 947769566735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769567983","data":{"timestamp":" 947769567983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769571513","data":{"timestamp":" 947769571513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769572509","data":{"timestamp":" 947769572508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769572771","data":{"timestamp":" 947769572771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769573722","data":{"timestamp":" 947769573722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769576607","data":{"timestamp":" 947769576607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769577654","data":{"timestamp":" 947769577653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769578131","data":{"timestamp":" 947769578130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769580484","data":{"timestamp":" 947769580484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769580568","data":{"timestamp":" 947769580568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" aa5bc04c-6124-4bbd-aba4-b81581ce10ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769594726","data":{"timestamp":" 947769594726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769597257","data":{"timestamp":" 947769597257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769600677","data":{"timestamp":" 947769600677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769603202","data":{"timestamp":" 947769603201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769605449","data":{"timestamp":" 947769605449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769607483","data":{"timestamp":" 947769607483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769612551","data":{"timestamp":" 947769612551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769614594","data":{"timestamp":" 947769614594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769616636","data":{"timestamp":" 947769616636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769618427","data":{"timestamp":" 947769618427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769621816","data":{"timestamp":" 947769621815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769623783","data":{"timestamp":" 947769623782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769627014","data":{"timestamp":" 947769627014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769629519","data":{"timestamp":" 947769629518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769638146","data":{"timestamp":" 947769638145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769640113","data":{"timestamp":" 947769640113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769641939","data":{"timestamp":" 947769641939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769643975","data":{"timestamp":" 947769643975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769646147","data":{"timestamp":" 947769646146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769649524","data":{"timestamp":" 947769649523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769651917","data":{"timestamp":" 947769651917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769653720","data":{"timestamp":" 947769653720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769655658","data":{"timestamp":" 947769655658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769658463","data":{"timestamp":" 947769658463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769660777","data":{"timestamp":" 947769660776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769662641","data":{"timestamp":" 947769662641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769664397","data":{"timestamp":" 947769664397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769666921","data":{"timestamp":" 947769666920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769669547","data":{"timestamp":" 947769669547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769671482","data":{"timestamp":" 947769671482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769674090","data":{"timestamp":" 947769674090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769675812","data":{"timestamp":" 947769675812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769677622","data":{"timestamp":" 947769677622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769679972","data":{"timestamp":" 947769679972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769682029","data":{"timestamp":" 947769682028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769684590","data":{"timestamp":" 947769684590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769686780","data":{"timestamp":" 947769686780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769689960","data":{"timestamp":" 947769689960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769691692","data":{"timestamp":" 947769691692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769694003","data":{"timestamp":" 947769694003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769694245","data":{"timestamp":" 947769694245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769694368","data":{"timestamp":" 947769694368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769735697","data":{"timestamp":" 947769735697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" c7e0af2a-c41d-4ec5-952e-ee7d320c1f83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769750263","data":{"timestamp":" 947769750263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769752430","data":{"timestamp":" 947769752430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769754354","data":{"timestamp":" 947769754354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769756898","data":{"timestamp":" 947769756898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769760342","data":{"timestamp":" 947769760342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769762067","data":{"timestamp":" 947769762067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769765842","data":{"timestamp":" 947769765842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769767656","data":{"timestamp":" 947769767656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769769649","data":{"timestamp":" 947769769649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769771921","data":{"timestamp":" 947769771921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769773844","data":{"timestamp":" 947769773843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769776648","data":{"timestamp":" 947769776648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769778875","data":{"timestamp":" 947769778875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769780978","data":{"timestamp":" 947769780977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769783056","data":{"timestamp":" 947769783056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769785604","data":{"timestamp":" 947769785604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769788249","data":{"timestamp":" 947769788249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769793623","data":{"timestamp":" 947769793623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769795264","data":{"timestamp":" 947769795264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769797289","data":{"timestamp":" 947769797289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769799547","data":{"timestamp":" 947769799547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769802024","data":{"timestamp":" 947769802024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769804211","data":{"timestamp":" 947769804210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769806433","data":{"timestamp":" 947769806433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769809139","data":{"timestamp":" 947769809138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769811469","data":{"timestamp":" 947769811468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769814570","data":{"timestamp":" 947769814570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIRARUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769817052","data":{"timestamp":" 947769817052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769819562","data":{"timestamp":" 947769819561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769823106","data":{"timestamp":" 947769823105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769825779","data":{"timestamp":" 947769825779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769829169","data":{"timestamp":" 947769829168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769831072","data":{"timestamp":" 947769831072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769833072","data":{"timestamp":" 947769833072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINDANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769834984","data":{"timestamp":" 947769834984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769836832","data":{"timestamp":" 947769836832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769838848","data":{"timestamp":" 947769838848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769841544","data":{"timestamp":" 947769841543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769843693","data":{"timestamp":" 947769843693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769848147","data":{"timestamp":" 947769848147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769851384","data":{"timestamp":" 947769851384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769853361","data":{"timestamp":" 947769853361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINDANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769855092","data":{"timestamp":" 947769855092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769857762","data":{"timestamp":" 947769857762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIWEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769860092","data":{"timestamp":" 947769860091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769862221","data":{"timestamp":" 947769862221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769864138","data":{"timestamp":" 947769864138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769866823","data":{"timestamp":" 947769866823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769869785","data":{"timestamp":" 947769869785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769873680","data":{"timestamp":" 947769873680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769878125","data":{"timestamp":" 947769878125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769880021","data":{"timestamp":" 947769880021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769882206","data":{"timestamp":" 947769882206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769884465","data":{"timestamp":" 947769884465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769887828","data":{"timestamp":" 947769887828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769887910","data":{"timestamp":" 947769887910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_085028"," gameId":" 8589f483-1694-484a-8f76-0a155f5cf797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}